kgbanswers.com 2017-12-02

# 542542 — kgb Privacy Policy

 1\. Introduction

The websites located at the domains www.kgb.com, www.thekgb.com, www.kgbkgb.com and kgb Mobile Applications (collectively, the “Sites”) are operated by kgb (“kgb” or “we” or “our” or “us”). Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected from you, what we do with it, with whom we share it, and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal data through the Sites. The Sites are operated in and controlled from the United States of America. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Sites, or if you wish to unsubscribe from services on any of the Sites for which you have previously registered, please contact us at accounts@kgb.com or at the address at the end of this policy.

**We encourage you to read and review this privacy policy carefully. By using our Sites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

2\. Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to your use of the Sites but not does apply to any third-party sites that may be linked to them or to any third-party entities listed on the Sites.

User information. If you create an account and join kgb in order to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the Sites, we ask for and record some “personal information.” “Personal Information” means information you knowingly choose to disclose to us, such as your name and email address. We may use your email address to send you updates and news about the Sites. You may choose not to receive email of this type and can do so through your “Account Settings” on www.kgb.com.

Contributions. We store and may publicly display your contributions to the Sites in order to provide and enhance the services that we offer. When we display your contributions, we may do so together with your user name. “Contributions” refers to any content you submit or post to any of the Sites for public display, such as ratings, comments, photos, facts, and other similar types of information. Please do not include information in your contributions that you expect to be kept private.

Feedback. If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content you provide in your communication so we can effectively respond to your communication.

Activity. We record information relating to your use of the Sites, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you visit, your browser or phone type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information, and other similar types of information. We use this information to operate and administer the Sites and to provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Sites. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information.

Enforcement. In certain cases, we may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the Sites (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

3\. Use of Information We Collect 

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our services, and to offer you other products, programs, or services we believe may be of interest to you.

We may use or disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

If we believe it is necessary, we may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good- faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (ii) enforce or apply our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy; (iii) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (iv) protect our rights, reputation, or property or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena, or other similar governmental request we may receive.

We may transfer your information to a third party in connection with a sale or acquisition of kgb or substantially all of its assets.

kgb may aggregate data and disclose such data only in aggregate and in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for marketing and promotional purposes (e.g., how many users responded to a particular offer). Aggregated information does not identify any User individually.

We use information about which links have been followed and whether action has been taken on another party’s website to improve our offerings and to customize the Service.

When you visit our Site, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Sites. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our website design and functionality.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

4\. Collection of Information by Third Parties and Sponsors 

The Sites may contain third-party advertisements or offers that are complementary to your use of kgb. If you choose to use these separate products or services, disclose information to the providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. You should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services.

5\. Cookies 

To enhance your experience with our Sites, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering on our Sites. However, once you choose to furnish any of the Sites with Personal Information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Sites (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to the Sites), and to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Sites may not work properly or at all.

6\. No Guarantees 

While this Privacy Statement expresses kgb’s standards for maintenance of private data, kgb is not in a position to guarantee the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in unintentional disclosure of data. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. But no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

7\. Data

Should you terminate your account, portions of your data may remain on our production and back-up servers indefinitely.

Any “personal information” you submit to any of our Sites can be viewed and used by other users and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. kgb is not responsible for your disclosure of any such information.

8\. Changes to This Policy 

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. You may review updates to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy at any time via links on our Sites. You agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of an annual or revised Privacy Policy on the Sites and that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this policy from time to time, so please review it regularly. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, and/or by means of a notice on our home page.

Kgb Contact Information

You can contact kgb with any questions or issues relating to this Privacy Policy at:

kgb

655 Madison Avenue, Third Floor

New York, NY 10065

Phone: (212) 909-8282
